JOHN MIGUEL ANGEL

FRONTEND DEVELOPER & DIGITAL DESIGN STUDENT



CONTACT

- +49 (0) 30 71079853
- im.mikel@hotmail.com
- Berlin, Germany

SKILLS

Technologies:

Java Script, Typescript

HTML5

CSS3

Sass

Bootstrap5

Node.js

React.js

Next.js

MongoDB

Express / Rest API

PROFILE

<Hi>

My name is Miguel, and I am delighted to introduce myself as a digital design student and frontend developer. I have a genuine passion for creating engaging user experiences that leave a positive impact. Drawing from my extensive background in customer service spanning over 8 years across various industries, I have developed a well-rounded skill set that blends design, development, team player and a strong customer-centric approach. Today, I would like to take you on a journey through my experiences, showcase my skills, and explore the exciting career paths that my diverse background has opened up for me. Let's embark on this exploration of the captivating world of digital design and frontend development together.

</Hi>

EDUCATION

Digital Design and Creation Degree, UOC University of

Catalunya,

OCT 2021- PRESENT

The Digital Design and Creation degree program treats design holistically, with special emphasis on techniques associated with graphic design, communication, and user experience (UX) design.

Psychology Modules

OCT 2021-OCT 2022

JOHN MIGUELANGEL

Other tools:

GitHub

VS Code

Canva

Illustrator

Photoshop

Jira

SOFT SKILLS

Communication

Creativity

Time Management

Problem Solving

Task Management

LANGUAGES

Spanish - Native

German - fluent

English - fluent

Full stack WebDev, DCI Digital Career Institute GmbH,

AUG 2022- JUN 2023

Full-Stack Web Developer (MERN)

Front-end: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap5, JavaScript, React.js, Rest-

API.

Back-end: Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB.

Hotel Management, SENA Colombia

FEB 2010- MAR 2012

Hotel management program is a degree based on environmental processes and sustainable development.

Web design and development technician, Colombia

FEB 2009 - DEC 2010

Technician in web design and development in html, css and php.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Nursing, Social work & Apprentice, Pro Seniore

Krankenheim Eichborndamm & Vivantes, Germany

JUL 2020 - AUG 2020

Helping patients effectively manage their routine.

Conveying Behavioral concerns and medically relevant symptoms to healthcare staff to optimize care delivery.

Senior Cabin Crew Member, Luftfahrtgesellschaft Walter, Germany

APR 2017 - MAR 2020

Resolved passenger situations during flights involving passengers and medical emergencies. Offered personalized assistance to children, elderly, and passengers with special needs.

JOHN MIGUELANGEL

Flight Attendant, Avianca, Colombia

JUL 2014 - JUN 2016

Facilitated efficient passenger onboarding process. Ensured safety and comfort of customers onboard aircraft.

Sales & Customer Service Agent, Colreservas,

Colombia

AUG 2013 - JUL 2014

Generated monthly sales for the department.

Served as the main point of contact for national and international clients.

Patient Coordinator, Psicólogos de la Salud, Colombia

SEP 2012 - MAY 2013

Managed patients' appointments.

SOCIAL MEDIA

